# Badal Kumar Behera

Senior Software Developer, Team Lead

zero2orbit@gmail.com

I am a Software Developer and my current team focuses on customizing software for financial institutions worldwide. I have 2 years of experience developing software using Opency, python, spring boot, and web technologies such as HTML, Javascript, and CSS.

7008050109



WORK EXPERIENCE

**Senior Software Developer**Misboi Consulting Services

06/2020 - Present www.misboi.com

Full-Stack Developer
Drubus Technologies Pvt Ltd

03/2019 - 05/2020 www.drubus.com Bhubaneswar, India

Bhubaneswar

Achievements/Tasks

- Successfully working on project Employee Time&Output Management (ETOM). Back-end(SpringBoot) and Frontend(HTML, CSS, JavaScript).
- Successfully build a Project DruSupport a online Ticketing System using **SpringBoot** as back-end and HTML, CSS, JavaScript as Front-end Technology.
- Working in Drusight Project as Component Developer build some components using *Opencv* and *Python*.
- Successfully build a Document Scanner Android app for Drusight Project using Opencv-Android, Android technology.

## **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of Technology

Gandhi Institute of Engineering and Technology, Gunupur

04/2016 - 03/2019

Odisha, India

Courses

 Computer Science & Engineering (CSE)

### **SKILLS**

Bhubaneswar, India

Python	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Spring Boot	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$
Node js	• • • • •
OpenCv	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$
Android	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$
Flutter	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$
ReactJs	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$

github.com/zero2orbit

### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

#### Developer Conner (10/2019 - 12/2019)

- Its is a social network for developers where a developer can communicate with each other and post their problems. Comment and Like on a post
- In this project for back-end, Node.js is used for Database MongoDb is used and for front-end, React.js is used

#### Weather App (01/2020 - 02/2020)

- its a weather checking website.
- In this project for back-end, Node.js is used for Database MongoDb is used and for front-end, HLML,CSS, JavaScriptis used.
- for weather data Some free **RestApi** services is used.

#### Onsite Service (07/2020 - Present)

- its it online service and grocery providing platform.
- For this project Node.js is used as back-end, MongoDB as DataBase and for Mobile Application Flutter is used.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English			0
Hindi			
Odia			

#### **INTERESTS**

Cricket | VollyBall

Travelling